Resynch: Travis for forom.com
Transcript: Chocolate for english.yyets.net
Wow. That's quite something.
Quite an honour.
I know.
They must be
impressed with you.
I didn't even know they had
an employee of the month.
Really? I thought
you won it once.
No, that was...
everyone thought I was dead.
A-ha.
Hmm, employee...
..of the month.
Yeah, it's,
it's a valued title.
Have you ever won it?
Er, no.
No.
I haven't.
I don't know, Jen, sometimes I think
it's because I just want it,
so damn much!
I am the employee of the month.
And yet, to a casual observer,
it'd appear that you do
very little around here.
Yeah, they must have
seen through that.
I think someone up there must
have sensed something in me.
Something I've always
known was there, er...
a greatness?
No, I'm not saying
that, but...something...
Yeah, yeah,
I'm sensing something.
Don't worry,
I won't let it go to my head.
Moss, guess who's won
employee of the month?
Roy.
No.
Richmond. No.
Harry.
Who's Harry?
The postman. No.
Me.
No.
I said Roy, right? Richmond?
Me!
Oh, about time!
Whatever happened to Richmond?
He got scurvy.
Can you be more specific?
I'm trying to picture your
role in Reynholm Industries.
Well, I'm the boss, head honcho,
numero uno, Mr Big,
The Godfather, Lord Of The Rings,
the Bourne Identity, er...
Taxi Driver, Jaws.
I forgot the question,
quite a while back. Who are you again?
I'm April Shepherd.
You're Richest magazine's Man Of
The Year. I'm doing the profile.
Oh yes, that's right.
I know you're the boss,
but what does that entail?
Oh, many things.
Like this morning,
for instance.
I had to choose the Employee
Of The Month, from the box.
May I ask,
what are you doing on that pad?
One of my little
hobbies is caricature.
Sometimes, I like to sketch
someone as I'm talking to them.
May I?
Well, I'm not very good.
I'm no Truman Capote.
Great, OK. Um...
I'll tell you what,
let's just do some quick-fire questions.
Maybe they'll give me an
insight into the real you.
OK.
Tell me, who's your favourite
person from history?
Sherlock Holmes.
Well, he's fictional.
Whoa! I think you'd better
check your facts there.
Fictional?
Who took care of the
business with the giant dog
that was eating everybody?
Well, it wasn't Watson.
Don't tell me,
I suppose he was fictional too.
Maybe there was no giant dog.
No, no, I think you're playing
games with me, young lady.
OK, then,
favourite fictional character.
Oh, ha-ha, ha!
The Elephant Man.
Tell you what,
let me widen the question out.
Favourite popular figure?
Churchill.
Well, what is it
you like about him?
I love the way he says,
"Oh, yes. Oh, yes."
I think, perhaps it's you
who's playing games with me.
You're a very surprising man,
Mr Reynholm.
Yes.
I am a surprising man.
April, may I take
you to dinner?
Oh, I don't think I could..
In Paris.
Paris?
Paris, yes. It's the name of
a new restaurant in Hull.
That's right,
we're going to Hull!
Hey, Roy, come over here.
Look at this.
"The biggest adventure
you can ever take
"is to live the life of your dreams" -
Oprah Winfrey.
I suppose that is the
biggest adventure.
Guys, come on in.
Sit down.
Is this a new desk?
Yeah, I thought I needed
some new furniture.
So, I got some stuff from upstairs.
Sit down, please.
I just thought, what with all
this extra attention on us...
on me, it might be worth
looking at ourselves and saying,
"Hey, am I really giving
it 110 per cent?"
And if not, "Why not?
What the heck is wrong with me?
"Am I mentally
ill or something?"
Roy, let's start with you.
When you're upstairs,
fiddling about with computers...
..would it hurt to smile?
Don't you realise what a
difference that would make?
Eh? Come on,
let's see a smile now, come on.
No, more warmth, warmer.
You're just showing more teeth,
that's not warmth.
I would say that's more of a
threatening look, actually.
I'll tell you what, Roy, keep at it.
That's your homework. Moss.
So, what's your speech
going to be about?
What speech?
Every employee of the
month has to give a speech
in their area of expertise.
Which for you is computers.
Where do I have to...?
At the monthly
shareholders meeting.
When do I have to...?
Friday.
What time...?
Morning.
How's that?
What's up, guys?
All right, Jen?
Urgh!
God! Just writing a speech.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
How's that going?
Good, good, good, good...
You know, I was thinking, er...
if there's anything
you guys wanna say,
I can put it in,
it's no problem.
Oh, oh, yeah, oh,
mm, interesting.
Um, is there anything you'd like
to say to the shareholders, Moss?
Just say, "Hi."
Say, "Hi," from us.
OK.
I love this.
I wonder how many more
times she's gonna come in.
I think, it'd be a good idea if
you two contributed to this, I do.
Oh, yeah. Why?
Hmm. I think,
I think it would give you experience
in writing a speech
for a public figure.
Well, obviously,
in our line of work that would be handy.
But, you know what, Jen,
I'm actually, I'm snowed under here.
Wait a second! Wait a second!
Oh, oh, what are we doing?
Eh?
We should write that speech!
What? Why?
Offer to write the speech.
No.
You have to! I can't!
She'll know something's
up if I do it!
Why would I do that?
Moss, do you trust me?
No.
Do you trust me?
If you trust me,
then offer to write that speech!
I. Don't. Trust. You.
Hello.
'I feel really bad having all
the fun writing this speech.'
Offer, offer, offer.
Well, I suppose we could write
the speech so that, you know,
you look like you know
what you're talking about.
Thanks, I'm off for lunch.
Leave it on my desk.
My God.
I know.
That's brilliant.
So, now you understand why we have
to write that speech for Jen.
She will say anything
we tell her to.
We can put any old bollocks in that
speech and she shall repeat it.
It's going to be hilarious.
Sometimes I could
kiss your mind, Roy.
OK, so let's just, um...
I don't know,
let's just throw around a few ideas.
OK. OK.
Ah...oh, could we tell her...
that there's an apple
inside every Apple Mac?
It's good. Yeah.
We could say that Bill
Gates is called Bill Gates,
because he owns a lot of gates.
Hmmm. That's good,
but it's not quite punchy enough,
and it's probably true now anyway.
I'll bet he does own a lot of gates.
He probably does.
It's got to be something big!
I think I may have it.
What?
You best put seatbelts
on your ears, Roy,
cos I'm gonna take them for
the ride of their lives!
Delightful.
Oh, no, no, no. You're silly.
Do you know, I've never been so
enchanted by a woman in all my life.
What's your name again?
I know you told me.
April.
Ah, what a charming name.
Always been one
of my favourites.
April, after dinner,
would you do me the honour
of accompanying me to my bed?
Oh, erm...
No, I've said too much!
I've let my heart overpower my head,
which is my wont.
But I don't care.
I find you enchanting.
And there's a condom
machine in the toilet.
I'm very flattered,
Douglas but, erm,
there's a problem. There's
something I should tell you. Go on.
Erm, I... I have a secret.
I could dance
around the subject,
but I like you, Douglas.
I want to be straight with you. Oh?
I used to be a man, Douglas.
I used to be a man.
I wish there was an easier
way of saying that,
but, believe me, there's not.
I've had a lot of hormone therapy
and a number of operations.
I'm really sorry.
I hope you don't
feel I deceived you.
I understand if you
would rather I left.
I don't care.
What?
Doesn't bother me.
Doesn't bother you at all?
It takes all sorts
to make a world.
Wow, it bothers most men.
I am not most men and
the offer still stands.
Are you up for it?
Amazing, just amazing.
You liked it?
You really know your
way around that area.
Well...
Tell me, what are you doing
tomorrow night, April?
I was thinking of staying
in and watching the darts.
You've read my mind.
# '60s Swing music
What is it?
This, Jen,
is the internet.
What?
That's right.
This is the internet?
The whole internet?
Yep.
I asked for a loan of it,
so that you could use it in your speech.
It's so small.
That's one of the
surprising things about it.
Hang on,
it doesn't have any wires or anything.
It's wireless.
Oh, yes,
everything's wireless nowadays, yeah.
I can use it in my speech?
What if someone needs it?
Oh, no, no, people will
still be able to go online.
It will still work.
Oh, good. Good.
I tell you,
you present this to the shareholders
and you will get
quite a response.
Can I touch it?
Ooh, it's so light.
Of course it is, Jen.
The internet doesn't weigh anything.
Ha-ha. No, of course it doesn't.
Ha-ha. Ha-ha.
Hey! What is Jen doing
with the internet?
Moss said I could
use it for my speech.
Are you insane?
What if she drops it?
I won't drop it,
I'll look after it.
No. No, no, no, no, Jen. No, this
needs to go straight back to Big Ben.
Big Ben?
It goes on top of Big Ben.
That's where you get the best reception.
I promise I won't let
anything happen to it.
No, Jen, I'm sorry. The elders of the
internet would never stand for it.
No, no, Roy. I spoke to the elders
of the internet, not one hour ago.
I told them Jen had won
employee of the month
and they were so impressed - wanted
to do whatever they could to help.
Wait a minute,
the elders of the internet?
The elders of the internet know who
I am? You've got to let me have it!
No, Jen, I'm sorry,
it's just too risky.
Oh, please, Roy.
Well, Moss,
has it been completely demagnetised?
By Stephen Hawking himself.
He sends his congratulations.
Well, if it's OK with the Hawk.
So, can I have it?
You can.
Oh, don't forget your speech.
Oh, thank you.
Slowly.
April, these past few days
have been like a dream.
Usually, I can't wait to get away
from a woman once I've ejaculated,
but with you,
I don't know, I feel alive.
April, I love you.
What?
That's right,
I totally love the bloody arse off you.
Oh, Douglas, I love you too.
Oh, poppet,
to think when we met, you were so
worried that you came from Iran.
What?
When we met. As if I'd be
worried about something like that.
I don't care where you're from.
Iran, France, doesn't bother me.
I'm very modern.
I'm not from Iran.
Well, you said something
along those lines.
No, not Iran, a man.
I said I used to be a man!
You used to be a man?
Yes!
Oh, God!
Well, we have a very interesting
talk lined up for today.
Our employee of the month,
and computer expert, Jen Barber,
has kindly agreed to say a few words
about her role in the IT department.
Now, speaking as someone who doesn't
know the difference between a laptop
and, erm, the larger one,
I'm certainly looking forward
to hearing what she has to say.
Good morning.
When I was asked
to give a speech
about what it is I do and everything,
I was very excited.
At last, I thought,
a chance to explain the wonders
of technology to ordinary folk.
But then I thought, "Who wants to
listen to a boring old speech?"
Wouldn't it be better
if I could actually bring one of
these wonders in to show you it?
Say, oh, I don't know,
the internet!
I think it would - and I have.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like to present to you the internet!
No flash photography,
you'll harm it.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Why's no-one laughing?
If anything were to
happen to this box,
the world as we know it
would fall into chaos.
Planes would drop from the sky,
like tables.
Society would tear itself apart
like an angry child with a napkin.
Man's primeval instinct
to survive at any cost,
would lead to terrible violence,
so, please,
no flash photography.
I must say this is all
very impressive, Douglas.
What exactly are
you working on?
I dunno.
April, we need to talk.
Darling, couldn't
we do this at home?
I was hoping we'd get
shit-faced and watch telly.
There'll be no more getting
shit-faced and watching telly.
There'll be no more
Steven Seagal marathons,
and there'll be no more
paintballing weekends.
I'm afraid our adventure
has come to an end.
What? But... But why?
It's not you, it's me.
No, actually it's not me,
it is you.
I'm sorry.
You don't think of me as a woman,
do you?
What? Of course I do!
It bothers you that
I used to be a man.
No, I love that you used to be a man.
It's your thing.
I love thinking
about that operation.
Oh, please, look at me.
I am a woman.
This is a woman in front of you.
Excuse me.
I am a woman!
You're tearing me apart.
Please, Douglas...
I'm sorry,
it's beyond my control.
Please, Douglas, please!
Just go.
You're making this
harder for me.
How could you do this?
How could you do this to me?!
You bastard.
And that's what the
flashing light's for.
Any more?
Is it heavy?
That's a bit of a silly question.
The internet doesn't
weigh anything.
OK, guys,
I guess I should wrap it up.
No, no.
I really have to finish up.
More! More! More! More!
Guys! Oh, my God,
you really like me.
This really isn't that funny.
I know, it's terrible.
I thought at least we'd
get a good story out it.
Something we'd remember.
It's over, April.
Oh, Jesus.
The internet!
Argh!
We're all gonna die!
Everybody, stay calm!
'He needs to hold his nerve...
'He's done it!'
But it's not the same.
Oh, April.
Resynch: Travis for forom.com
Transcript: Chocolate for english.yyets.net